Wow. Wow. So you see the quality?
This is exactly what we predicted from an Adobe product, you know, and yes, it's as you see
perfect. So we can clip on open, we can click on open in Photoshop web in order to edit it.
But as you see, Firefly doesn't have an editor itself. It's clear, you know, and it was
pretty stable because Adobe owns the most powerful photo editing software in the world, which is
Photoshop, you know, and it doesn't come and create a cheaper clone of it inside another product.
It just refers you to the very Photoshop that it has, right? So we can, as you see, open this
image in Photoshop web as well. And what else do we have? Let me close this one.
Yep. Something went wrong. Okay. I reload.
And yes, as you see, something went wrong. So the generated image was disappeared all of a sudden.
I also tried resubmitting my command, but I have not gotten anything yet from it.
But as you see, it is a pretty powerful tool when it comes to generating images.